# Skyler Thompson

(123) 456-7890 skylerthompson0example,com <u>Linked In | Portfolio</u> 123 Bridge Street, Boston, MA 12345

A patient-focused RN with 12+ years of experience in post-operative care and rehabilitation. Administered patient-centered care using individual care plans. Achieved consistently high levels of patient satisfaction by delivering compassionate care and emotional support.

# **Key Skills**

- Patient-Centered Care
- Nurse Management
- Case Management
- Process Improvement
- Trauma Care

# **Professional Experience**

#### Registered Nurse

Boston Medical Center, Boston, MA | November 2016 - Present

- Communicate empathetically with diverse patients, build rapport, and drive the delivery of patient-centered care to achieve a 94% patient satisfaction rating
- Support an interdisciplinary team with direct nursing care for patients and assist with developing care plans to improve patient outcomes
- Lead, mentor, and coach a team of more than 15 LPNs and identify opportunities to enhance clinical workflows, resulting in a 10% reduction in average wait times

#### Registered Nurse

St. Luke's Hospital, Boston, MA I May 2011 - November 2016

- Coordinated with nursing teams and physicians to improve clinical operations, patient intake, and discharge, which increased the number of patients seen in 30 minutes or less from 72% to 80%
- Conducted comprehensive assessments for new patients and prepared individualized care plans with physicians for a 175-bed unit

## Education

Master of Science (B.S.) Nursing

Harvard University, Cambridge, MA September 2014 - May 2016

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Nursing

Boston College, Boston, MA September 2007 - May 2011

## Certifications

- Advanced Practice Registered Nurse (APRN), 2016
- Registered Nurse, State of Massachusetts, License #123456, 2011
- Advanced Pediatric Life Support, American Heart Association 2011